Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/yetiskol (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Management Consulting Customer Experience Analytics

Languages

Turkish (Native or Bilingual) English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Introduction to Marketing
edX Verified Certificate for
Fundamentals of Statistics
Probability - The Science of
Uncertainty and Data
Machine Learning Specialization

Honors-Awards

Francis E. Brady Memorial Award Kennet S. Moffitt Scholarship John B. and Catherine B. Nelson/ McGraw Foundation Endowed Scholarship

2nd Best Stock Pitch of National Organization for Business and Engineering(NOBE) Engineering Economy Stock Pitch Competition

Top 10 student, 2011 and 2012 Science Olympiads - Biology

Omer Y.

Senior Product Manager | Product Management, Data Analytics New York, New York, United States

Summary

I'm a product manager with experience in complex and highly regulated industries such as InsurTech and FinTech. With experience at YC-backed startups, I thrive in fast-paced environments where I can tackle complex challenges head-on with passionate teams.

Currently, at Vouch, I'm:

- Developing products that empower our Insurance Team to create cutting-edge insurance products
- Exploring applications of LLMs in the insurance industry

Beyond work, you'll often find me:

- Experimenting with AI applications (I'm constantly maxing out my Claude credits.)
- Exploring the local food scene (I'm a huge fan of Anthony Bourdain.)
- Working out at my local gym

I'm eager to connect with fellow builders and learners who share my enthusiasm for solving problems -- or finding hidden gems.

Experience

Vouch Insurance Senior Product Manager 2022 - Present (2 years)

Embarked on a mission to revolutionize insurance underwriting. I'm helping transform centuries-old processes into streamlined, digital workflows with the help of LLMs/AI.

Zeplin

Product Analyst 2021 - 2022 (1 year)

San Francisco Bay Area

- Joined as the first data hire on a quest to unlock the power of analytics.
- Led the planning and implementation of the data analytics infrastructure

Stockpile

3 years

Product and Data Analytics Lead 2020 - 2021 (1 year)

Rode the startup rollercoaster from 20 to 80 employees:

- Wore every hat imaginable from customer support to product.
- Rolled my sleeves to code tools that made our teams' lives easier
- Replaced backend services and data infrastructure
- Reimagined user experiences
- Hired a team of 3 from scratch
- and more...

Product Management & Analytics 2018 - 2020 (2 years) Palo Alto, CA

Connors Group Associate Consultant 2017 - 2017 (less than a year) Greater Pittsburgh Area

Accenture

Business Analyst 2016 - 2016 (less than a year)

- Assisted a global European retailer to optimize its assortment and prices in the EMEA region

Education

Penn State University
Bachelor's Degree, Industrial Engineering